{
  "title": "Short Idioms Exam",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "After their argument, John didn't know if Rick was a friend or ........",
      "answers": ["Blood", "Rival", "Fiend", "Foe"],
      "correct": "Foe"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Many Christians believe your body and ........ belong to God",
      "answers": ["Soul", "Reason", "Brain", "Heart"],
      "correct": "Soul"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Joanne left abruptly â€” without rhyme or ........",
      "answers": ["Verse", "Reason", "Cause", "Record"],
      "correct": "Reason"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Ben estimated how much wear and .........the new tires",
      "answers": ["tear", "abuse", "effect", "impact"],
      "correct": "tear"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "He is head over ........ about his new girlfriend.",
      "answers": ["heart", "body", "backwards", "heels"],
      "correct": "heels"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "He bent over ........ to please his boss but the manager was never satisfied. ",
      "answers": ["forward", "backwards", "both ways", "sideways"],
      "correct": "backwards"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": " Nicole's promotion and added workload kept her as busy as a ........",
      "answers": ["fox", "bird", "horse", "bee"],
      "correct": "bee"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Mandy's children are her flesh and ........ so they always come first on her priority list.",
      "answers": ["blood", "water", "soul", "friend"],
      "correct": "blood"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "On Jen and Brad's very first date, she could tell he was as cunning as a ........",
      "answers": ["puppy", "bear", "fox", "wolf"],
      "correct": "fox"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Before Tom headed into the forest, he made sure he had packed his bow and ........",
      "answers": ["shotgun", "back pack", "canteen", "arrows"],
      "correct": "arrows"
    }
  ]
}
